Finding aid to the Kiki Hunter Smith papers CA.MS.00089
Smith College Archives
Kiki Hunter Smith papers
1967-1971
Smith College Archives
Smith, Catherine (Kiki) Hunter, 1949-
CA.MS.00089
0.625 linear feet (2 containers)
The Kiki Hunter Smith papers relate to her years at Smith College (as an undergraduate student). Types of materials include academic work, appointment books, correspondence, diaries, photographs, resumes, Freshman Carnival information, Sophomore PUSH songs, Junior Ushers paperwork, student government documents such as letters to class representatives and flyers for events, and Morris House memorabilia.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Kiki Smith donated her letters, diaries, appointment books and other papers from her years at Smith College to the College Archives in the Spring of 2000.
Biographical / Historical
Kiki Smith was born Catherine Hunter Smith on December 4, 1949 to Dr. and Mrs. Arthur M. Smith. She attended St. Anne's School in Charlottesville, Virginia prior to her enrollment at Smith College. Smith majored in Theater, with minors in English and Art. She was Class President for both her junior and senior years. After receiving an MA in Drama with emphasis in history and directing from the University of Virginia and an MFA with emphasis in costume and lighting design from the University of Texas, she returned to Smith College as an Instructor in Theatre and Speech, 1974 - 1977; Assistant Professor of Theatre and Speech, 1977 - 1986; Associate Professor of Theatre and Speech, 1986 - 1995, and Professor of Theatre and Speech, 1995- present. Smith also served as Dean of Freshmen, 1983 - 1986; and Associate Dean of the Faculty, 1990 - 1992.
Related Material
12. TR - 80. Cla 1970 Com Panel
42. Faculty - Smith, Catherine (Kiki) Hunter
Sophian, April 7, 1977, p. 10
Scope and Contents
The Kiki Hunter Smith relate to her years spent at Smith College as an undergraduate student, dating from 1967 to 1971. Types of materials include academic work, appointment books, correspondence, diaries, photographs, resumes, Freshman Carnival information, Sophomore PUSH songs, Junior Ushers paperwork, student government documents such as letters to class representatives and flyers for events, and Morris House memorabilia, including a freshman house handbook.
Smith, Catherine Hunter, 1949-; Smith College--Students.
- Appointment Books, 1969-70 (Box 2252.1, Folder 1)
- Class Notes: Theatre 211a, 251b, 1970 (Box 2252.1, Folder 2)
- Class Notes: Theatre 304b, 1971 (Box 2252.1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence from, Oct 1967 - Dec 1968 (Box 2252.1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence from, Jan 1969 - Jul 1971; undated (Box 2252.1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence to, Apr 1967 - Dec 1968 (Box 2252.1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence to, Feb 1969 - May 1971; undated (Box 2252.1, Folder 7)
- Diaries, Sept 1968 - May 1968 (Box 2252.1, Folder 8)
- Freshman Year Documents, 1967-68 (Box 2252.2, Folder 1)
- Sophomore Year Documents, 1968-69 (Box 2252.2, Folder 2)
- Junior Year Documents, 1969-70 (Box 2252.2, Folder 3)
- Senior Year Documents, 1970-71 (Box 2252.2, Folder 4)
- General, undated (Box 2252.2, Folder 5)
- Morris House Documents, 1967; undated (Box 2252.2, Folder 6)
- Photographs, undated (Box 2252.2, Folder 7)
- Resume, 1971 (Box 2252.2, Folder 8)